NATAN MESELE

Leadership & PROGRAMMER



Profile

My name is Natan Mesele. I graduated from Infolink University College with a degree in Computer Science. I scored a good grade of 3.83 GPA & Also, in 2014, I graduated also from Infolink University College Masters of Business Administration with a 3.8 with a very good research result. I have more than 4 years of work experience in total.

Experience

2010 - 2012 Rift valley University, Atlas college

Instructor, Hawassa

Instructor in computer science department & TVET coordinator

2013 - Present Zion College, Unique star college

Computer science department Head, Ha

wassa

Computer science department Head &

Instructor in computer science

department

Education

2006 - 2009 Computer science

Infolink University College, Hawassa The study of computers and other computational systems is computer

science.

2013 - 2014 Masters of Business Administration

(MBA)

Infolink University College, Hawassa An MBA is offers both academic and practical instruction in business or investment Management.

Interests

Interest

Read a book and Also, taking actions that will help me change my life, Outdoor activities., Community service, Playing music instrument

Skills Skill group Ability to perform work properly Management skill Communication skill Skill group Problem-solving skills Active listening Customer service skills

Contact

- ☐ Ethiopia, Hawassa
- +251926412563 / +251939602491
- □ huluale12@gmail.com
- □ Natan Mesele
- □ @Nathan_mesele1
- ☐ Di Natalie Nathan Mesele